Guide to the Paul Berg Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2001-092
  - Beckman Fundraising 1980-1989:
    - CMGM Fundraising correspondence (Box 9)
    - Funding for CMGM Center (Box 9)
    - Academic Plan for CMGM 8/84 (Box 9)
    - Original Program in Medical Genetics 1981 (Box 9)
    - CMGM Search Committees (Box 9)
    - Center for Molec. & Genetic Med. Committee (Box 9)
    - HHMI Policies for Investigators (Box 9)
    - Relations between HHMI and CMGM (Box 9)
    - Hughes Institute materials (Box 9)
    - Correspondence with Purnell Choppin (Box 9)
    - A. Beckman Matters 9/84 (Box 9)
    - Second Appeal to Beckman (Box 9)
    - Fairchild Foundation (Box 9)
    - Markey Foundation (Box 9)
    - Markey Proposal II (Box 9)
    - Mather Foundation matters (Box 9)
    - Dealings with SKB (Box 9)
    - The SKB Agreement (Box 9)
    - Correspondence with Wendt & Dealings with SKB gifts (Box 9)
    - George & Camilla Smith Foundation (Box 9)
    - Zaffaroni file (Box 9)
    - MGM 5/10/85 (Box 9)
    - Scientific Symposium 20 Anniversary 3/27-28/80 (Box 9)
    - PPG Discussions (Box 9)
    - Sandoz (Box 9)
    - Dupont file (Box 9)
    - Steve Jobs (Box 9)
    - Bob Swanson – Genentech (Box 9)
    - Beckman Symposium 10/17/85 (Box 9)
    - The Beckman Naming Occasion (Box 9)
    - General Fundraising (Box 9)
    - Correspondence with Jack Whitehead (Box 9)
    - Communications with Mrt. Li Ka-shing (Box 9)
    - Gerson Bakar (Box 9)
    - David Blech (Box 9)
    - Syntex – Rosenkranz and Allen (Box 9)
    - Bob Noyce file (Box 9)
    - Colton (Box 9)
    - Brook Byers Foundation (Box 9)
    - Ron Cape (Box 9)
    - Weingart Foundation (Box 9)
    - [unlisted folders] (Box 9)
  - [NIH Grant - unlisted folders] (Box 10)
  - Program in Molec. & Genetic Medicine members (Box 10)
  - AAAS (Box 11)
  - Beckman Symposium 10/12/85 (Box 11)
  - Erik Boye (Box 11)
  - Karol Taylor (Box 11)
  - Elman Walde (Box 11)
  - Michael O'Donnell (Box 11)
  - David Bramhill (Box 11)
  - Roger Kasken (Box 11)
  - James Flynn Jr. (Box 11)
  - Kazuhisa Sekimizu (Box 11)
  - Fellowship Programs (Box 11)
  - Hisaji Maki (Box 11)
  - Kornberg Symposium 5/88 (2) (Box 11)
  - Beckman Management Group (Box 11)
  - 1991 Markey Trust Proposal (Box 11)
  - Industrial Affliliates (Box 11)
  - Wm. Freeman & Co. (Box 11)
  - LSRF (Box 11)
  - NSF (Box 11)
  - Nobel Committee (3) (Box 11)
  - Franco-Amer Assn for Fetal Med (Box 11)
  - Pre-'89 Correspondence F, G, M (Box 11)
  - Pre-'89 Correspondence A-E, H-L, N-Z (Box 12)
  - Rockefeller Board (Box 12)
  - Trip files 1996 (Box 12)
  - Trip files 1996-97 (Box 13)
  - Videos of talks at The Welch Foundation Chemical Conference 1993 (Box 13)
  - Man's tie with A. Beckman image (Box 13)
  - Course materials, 1996 (Box 14)
  - Trip files 1994 (Box 14)
  - Trip files 1995-97 (Box 15)
  - Videos (Box 15)
  - Unlisted files (Box 16)
  - Videos (Box 16)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2007-051
  Student records are restricted for 75 years from date of graduation.
  - Grad students
    - Arndt- John, Donna (Box 7)
    - Addresses of former group members (Box 7)
    - Bretsdev, Mark (Box 7)
    - Bnaerjee, Ronadip (Box 7)
    - Mantevil-Brutlag, Simone (Box 7)
    - Buchman, Andy (Box 7)
    - Barsoum, James (Box 7)
    - Baldwin, Anne Norris (Box 7)
    - Clanedar, Rich (Box 7)
    - Clark, Steve (Box 7)
    - Carbon, John (Box 7)
    - Canaani, Dan (Box 7)
    - Chamberlin, Michael (Box 7)
    - Chambers, Ian Paul (Box 7)
    - Chu, Gilbert (Box 7)
    - Cuzin, Francois (Box 7)
    - Cruz, Myra (Box 7)
    - Cole, Charles (Box 7)
    - Dieckmann, Marianne (Box 7)
    - Diaz, Elva (Box 7)
    - DePamphilis, Mel (Box 7)
    - Doerfler, Walter (Box 7)
    - Donoho, Greg (Box 7)
    - Dulbecco, Renato (Box 7)
    - Arnanz, Montserrat (Box 7)
    - Firmenich, Antoine (Box 7)
    - Folk (Box 7)
    - Fromm, Mike (Box 7)
    - Gassmann, Max (Box 7)
    - Garren, Ron (Box 7)
    - Geller, Al (Box 7)
    - Goff, Steve (Box 8)
    - Hacohen, Nir (Box 8)
    - Hayakawa, Dr. Hiroshi (Box 8)
    - Hays, Sharon, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Higgins, Mark (Box 8)
    - Hofstetler, Hans (Box 8)
    - Hill, Charles (Box 8)
    - Holland, Eric (Box 8)
    - Hsu, Ming-ta (Box 8)
    - Howard, Bruce (Box 8)
    - Igarashi, Koiche (Box 8)
    - Iaccarino, M. (Box 8)
    - Jessberger, Rolf (Box 8)
    - Kadesh, Tom (Box 8)
    - Unlabeled folder with photos (Box 8)
    - Jasin, Maria (no label on folder) (Box 8)
    - Konner, Jason (Box 8)
    - Kirk-Felton, Libby (Box 8)
    - Kawakami, Christine (Box 8)
    - Kornberg, Roger (Box 8)
    - Kroeger, Chris (Box 8)
    - Krushelnycky, Bohdan (Box 8)
    - Lagerkvist (Box 8)
    - Lewis, Susanna (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Littauer, Uriel (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Muenck, Karl (Box 1)
    - Luria, Sylvie (Box 1)
    - Magnusson, Govan (Box 1)
    - Margolskee, Bob (Box 1)
    - Mark, David (Box 1)
    - McPhail, Mike (Box 1)
    - Mertz, Janet (Box 1)
    - Morrow, John (Box 1)
    - Morrison, Sherie (Box 1)
    - Mulligan, Richard (Box 1)
    - Mukherjee, Siddhartha (Box 1)
    - Nichols, J. F. (Box 1)
    - Nordloh (Box 1)
    - Ogunmola, Prof G. B. (Box 1)
    - Ofengand (Box 1)
    - Peabody, Dave (Box 1)
    - Ozawa, Clare (Box 1)
    - Ostrem, Dennis (Box 1)
    - Okayama, Hiroto (Box 1)
    - Primakoff, Paul (Box 1)
    - Pontius, Brian (Box 1)
    - Reichardt, Jurgen (Box 1)
    - Rathmell, Kim (Box 1)
    - Remtulla, Ally (Box 1)
    - Reichard, Peter (Box 1)
    - Schreiber, Edgar (Box 1)
    - Rigby, Peter (Box 1)
    - Scott, Christopher (no folder) (Box 1)
    - Shenk, Tom (Box 1)
    - Sklar, Jeff (Box 1)
    - Shishido, Kazuo (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Smith, Andrew – 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Southern, Peter (Box 2)
    - Soll, Larry (Box 2)
    - Smith, Brad (Box 2)
    - Strehlow, David (Box 2)
    - Stuhlmann, Heidi (Box 2)
    - Symans, R. H. (Box 2)
    - Suresh, Subramani (Box 2)
    - Theland, Lars (Box 2)
    - Yarus, M (Box 2)
    - Tomasson, Mike (Box 2)
    - Wilson, John (Box 2)
    - Walberg, Mark (Box 2)
    - Villareal, L. (Box 2)
    - Trager, Jacqueline (Box 2)
    - Yamiu (Box 2)
    - White, Ty (Box 2)
    - Wood, B.W. (Box 2)
    - Wong, Brian (Box 2)
    - You, Ji Chang (Box 2)
    - Zierler, Helge (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Zemelman, Boris (Box 2)
  - Strain notebooks – 4 volumes with sections labeled with individual (student?) names (Box 3)
  - Berg Reprints, circa 1979-1996 (Box 4)
  - Berg Reprints (Box 5)
  - External Science Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Univ Colorado Health Science Center, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Joklik Symposium, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Beckman Grants Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Annenberg Symposium, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Rockefeller Board, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Stanford Alumni (2 folders), 1992 (Box 5)
  - Juan March Foundation, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Mel Cohn Symposium, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Weizmann Dinner, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Yanofsky Award, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Cornell keynote, NYC n.d. (Box 5)
  - Personal correspondence (Box 5)
  - Biochem 202 extra handouts (Box 5)
  - CMGM Executive Committee
    - minutes, 1982-1988 (Box 5)
    - minutes, 1982-87 (Box 5)
    - Directorate, minutes, 1982-84 (Box 5)
  - PMGM Seminars, 1995/96 (Box 6)
  - Spectrum nametags – no folder (Box 6)
  - Biological Sciences (Box 6)
  - Developmental Biology (Box 6)
  - Cancer Biology (Box 6)
  - Spectrum Photos- envelope no folder (Box 6)
  - Spectrum, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Spectrum Expenses (Box 6)
  - Spectrum Expenses – unfoldered material (Box 6)
  - Spectrum program (Box 6)
  - Binder – PMGM New Faculty Recruitment (Box 6)
  - Biochem Department files—may not have listed every file (Box 9)
  - Biochemisry Affiliate Program (Box 9)
  - Biochem Faculty reports (Box 9)
  - Bichem Founders Fund (Box 9)
  - Biochem general (Box 9)
  - Lab spaces (Box 9)
  - Grad admission interviews (Box 9)
  - Heller lecture (Box 9)
  - Stanford Art Committee (Box 9)
  - Stanford Center for Biomedical Ethics (Box 9)
  - Biotechnology-Law Course (Box 9)
  - Cahill Chair (Box 9)
  - Stanford Clinical Cancer Center (Box 9)
  - Consulting/Conflict of Interest matters (Box 9)
  - Dean Funding (Box 9)
  - Dean’s Task Force on PhD training (Box 9)
  - Faculty Campaign Planning Committee (Box 9)
  - Stanford Gene therapy Task Force (Box 9)
  - Indirect Cost Debate (Box 9)
  - LCME Accrediation (Box 9)
  - Lohrlein, Christine (Box 9)
  - Millenial Forum (Box 9)
  - Stanford –NIH (Box 9)
  - Videos and books (Box 10)
  - Affiliation files (Box 11-12)
  - Service with non-Stanford organizations, foundations, etc. (Box 12)
  - Genome testimony files (Box 12)
- Profiles in Science site on Paul Berg [computer files], Accession ARCH-2009-127
- Lecture notes and Nobel Prize files, 1978-1998
  - Nobel Prize trip, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Telegrams, 1980 Oct (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - News clippings, 1980 Oct (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Congratulatory letters (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Letters, 1980 Oct (Box 2, Folder 6)